{
    "subject": "Craig_Ferguson",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "I'll_Be_There__film_",
    "human_readable": "Craig Ferguson acted in the film I'll Be There.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9743762612342834,
            "question": "Did Craig Ferguson star in a film called 'I'll Be There'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9713897109031677,
            "question": "Craig Ferguson acted in which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9653787016868591,
            "question": "In which movie did Craig Ferguson have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9345201253890991,
            "question": "Name a film starring Craig Ferguson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9061780571937561,
            "question": "What film did Craig Ferguson act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803978562355042,
            "question": "Is Craig Ferguson an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.872663140296936,
            "question": "Has Craig Ferguson appeared in any films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7972290515899658,
            "question": "Who starred in the film 'I'll Be There'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.791206955909729,
            "question": "What is the title of the film with Craig Ferguson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7140355706214905,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Craig Ferguson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Craig Ferguson acted in the film I'll Be There.",
            "html": "yago_6314_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film with Craig Ferguson?",
            "html": "yago_6314_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who starred in the film 'I'll Be There'?",
            "html": "yago_6314_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Craig Ferguson appeared in any films?",
            "html": "yago_6314_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6314_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6314/re-ranker-msmarco/86.txt, it is mentioned that \"I\u2019ll Be There was a particular case in point because not only is Ferguson making his directing debut but he was actually an actor whose career has been blighted by a string of roles in low-budget movies like The Big Tease and Modern Vampires.  As the eight other people in the audience of my local cinema will testify on the night I went to see it, I\u2019ll Be There was flat and characterless.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6314/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt, it is mentioned that \"In 2003, he made his directorial debut with \u201cI\u2019ll Be There,\u201d which he also wrote and starred in.\"\n\nThe information suggests that Craig Ferguson acted in the film I'll Be There.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Craig Ferguson was an actor and mentions his role in the film \"I'll Be There\" from 2003. Therefore, it supports the statement that Craig Ferguson acted in the film \"I'll Be There.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}